译者/微博@Emtee
字幕转制：天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
嘿
Hey!
你个…
You...
…小…
...little...
…怂包
...pussy.
硬核亨利
你好 亨利
Hello, Henry.
你说不了话  但这正常
You can't speak, but that's normal.
好吧 这不正常 但只是暂时的 好吗
Well, it isn't normal, but it's only temporary, okay?
你记得你怎么到这里来的吗
Do you remember how you got here?
没事
That's fine.
这也正常
That's normal, too.
亨利 等等
Henry, wait.
等等
Wait.
我们慢慢来
We'll get there.
扫描
Scan.
已激活感官处理器
Sensory processor activated.
放松 好吗
Relax, okay?
扫描中
Scanning.
- 已确认视讯连接  - 上去
- Video link confirmed.  - Up.
下一步可能会疼
This next part might hurt.
或许很疼
Maybe quite a lot.
但不会持续很久 我保证
But it won't last long, I promise.
快好了
Almost there.
焊接器
Welder.
你能行
You can do it.
好样的 亨利
Wonderful, Henry.
握紧
Squeeze.
再用力些
Harder.
很棒 对吗
Cool, right?
覆肤器
Integument?
手别动
Please don't move your hand.
你可能想不起来了
You probably don't recall.
你一直都不太喜欢我的工作
You were never a big fan of my work.
或许这会改变你的想法
Maybe this will change your mind.
对吗
Right?
记忆是一样有趣的东西
Memory's a funny thing.
我是专家 而我不知道你是否能恢复记忆
I'm an expert and I don't know if you'll ever get yours back.
你完全不记得我了 是吗 亨利
You don't remember me at all, do you, Henry?
我叫艾丝黛尔
My name is Estelle.
你和我曾是…
You and I were...
我们仍旧是…
we still are...
…夫妻
...husband and wife.
我爱你 亨利
I love you, Henry.
我等不及想听你说出口了
I can't wait to hear you say it.
亨利
Henry.
他的记忆还在恢复
His memories are still catching up with him.
天呐
Oh, Jesus.
我是罗比
I'm Robbie.
声音魔术师
The sorcerer of sound.
你会喜欢这东西的
You are gonna love this.
因为 先生…
Because, sir...
你将选择你自己的声音
you're gonna get to pick your own voice.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
你好 亨利
Hello, Henry.
罗比
Robbie.
拜托 它们都是可选的  什么白人不想
Oh, come on, they're options. What white guy wouldn't wanna
声音像路易·阿姆斯特朗呢 就再玩一次 很快
sound like Louis Armstrong? Just one more. Quick.
亨利 我是你的父亲
Henry, I am your father.
罗伯特 够了
Robert, enough.
对不起 妈妈
Sorry, Mom.
我们用亨利的声音如何
How about we use Henry's voice?
好 随便 你说了算 无聊
Yeah, whatever you say. You're the boss. Boring.
遭到入侵 等级为四
Security breach, level four.
- 这是演习吗  - 什么情况
- Is this a drill?  - What is this?
等级为四
Level four.
- 关上门  - 可能是误报
- Lock the door.  - It's probably a mistake.
艾丝黛尔 呼叫基地
Estelle, call the base.
遭到入侵 等级为四
Security breach, level four.
已清查
已清查　已清查
已清查　已清查　已清查
不是吧
Oh, no.
没错
Yes.
谢谢
Spasiba.
起来
Get up.
亨利 是吗
Henry, right?
- 请别这样  - 闭嘴
- Please, don't.  - Shut up.
你觉得新的你怎么样
How do you like the new you?
我打断进程了吗
Did I interrupt the procedure?
亨利还不能说话吗
Can Henry not talk yet?
没错 他还不能
No, he can't. No.
亨利 别那样看我
Don't look at me like that, Henry.
你这个女朋友或许重建了你
Your girlfriend here might have rebuilt you,
但给她原材料使用的是我
but I gave her the raw materials to work with.
我是说非常非常原生的材料
And I mean really, really raw materials.
- 你叫什么  - 提摩西
- What's your name?  - Timothy.
很高兴见到你 提摩西
Nice to meet you, Timothy.
艾丝黛尔把亨利的遗骸带来时 你看见没
Did you see Henry when Estelle brought his remains here?
看见了
Yeah.
你能向亨利描述下
Would you please be so kind to describe them to better Henry's
让他知道他现在看上去有多棒吗
understanding of how good he looks now?
当然 他肘部以下的…
Sure. His arm was shot off below the...
手臂被打掉了…
below the elbow and the...
膝盖以下的腿也被打掉了
the leg shot off below the knee.
还有个足球大小的凹痕…
And there was a football-sized dent...
你有正好看到他的头吗
Did you happen to see his head?
- 有  - 说
- Yes.  - Do tell.
头骨被打凹了 还有…
Um, the skull was dented in and there was this, um...
他的双眼不见了 他下巴的后半部分…
his eyes were missing and, um, the bottom half of his jaw was
被打得粉碎
shred to pieces.
差不多
Just about right.
我也流血了 刚有点费劲
I'm bleeding, too. That was a little strenuous.
跟紧了
Stay close.
亨利 快
Henry! Hurry up!
把它关上
Close it.
亨利 快来
Henry, come on!
亨利 快跟上
Henry, try to keep up!
嘘 快来
Shh. Come on.
踢开它
Kick it in.
快来
Come on.
如果阿肯得到我的成果 这些人会被复活
If Akan gets ahold of my work, men like these will be
用来组成他的军队
brought back from the dead to form his army.
快走
Go!
紧急出口
亨利 别
Henry, no!
亨利
Henry!
抓住我的手
Take my hand!
已启用逃生舱
Escape pod initiated.
有两个逃生舱
There are two pods.
- 一个  - 马迪？
- One.  - Marty?
抱歉 那人明显疯了
Sorry. The man's clearly gone insane.
马迪 别这样
Marty, no!
亨利
Henry.
这是你的 进去
It's yours. Get in.
艾丝黛尔
Estelle!
进去 进去
Get in! Get in!
已启用逃生舱
Escape pod initiated.
高度…
Altitude...
降落伞 降落伞 打开降落伞
The chute! The chute! Pull the chute!
太快了 太快了
It's going too fast! It's going too fast!
稳住 亨利
Hold on, Henry!
天啊 阿肯的雇佣兵
Oh, God. Akan's mercenaries.
放我下来 放我下来
Put me down. Put me down!
亨利
Henry.
他们低估你了 好吗
They underestimate you, okay?
让他们靠近 然后你就攻击
Let them get close and then engage.
阿肯 这也是个弱鸡
攻击
Engage!
不 亨利 反击 快
No. Henry! Fight back! Come on!
住手
No, stop it!
你男朋友不是你期望的杀人机器？
不过你造了个很棒的拳击袋
住手 住手
You stop it! Stop it!
- 怎么了  - 住手
- What?  - Stop it!
艾丝黛尔…
Estelle...
你不好奇这玩意儿会对这混蛋怎样吗
不要 不要
No! No!
你他妈就是只受到惊吓的兔子 对吧
You're a fucking rabbit in the headlights, aren't you?
没事的 我不会伤害你
It's all right. I'm not here to hurt you.
你的语音模组装了吗
Is your speech module installed?
见鬼
Shit.
好吧 至少我们知道你不聋
Well, at least we know you're not deaf.
好了 现在把手放下吧
It's all right. You can put your hands down now.
三年来 我一直在等待这一刻
Three years I've been waiting for this moment and I get
却等到个该死的查理·卓别林 真他妈见鬼 快来
Charlie fucking Chaplin. Fuck's sake, come on!
好了 我们来查看下你
All right, let's have a look at you.
请打开手套箱
Open the glove box, please.
拿出那整个奇特的装置
Take out that whole contraption.
你得解开电线
You gotta untangle the wires.
那是枚结婚戒指吗
Is that a wedding ring?
你…你结婚了吗
Are you... are you married?
结果怎么样
How's that working out for you?
是啊 真令人震惊 好了
Yeah, what a shocker. Right.
下面我要你 脱掉衣服
Next, I need you to, uh, take your shirt off, please.
打开那儿 没错 那些东西
Open up there. Yeah, those.
把插头插进插座
Plug the jacks in there.
没错 插进去
Yeah, in there.
你叫亨利 还有…好吧
So, your name's Henry and...okay, well,
好消息是你会存活一段时间
the good news is that you're gonna live a while.
坏消息是 这种情况下 一段时间是指最多
The bad news is that in this case, a while means 20,
二三十分钟 亨利
30 minutes tops, Henry.
除非你运气非常非常好
Unless you're very, very lucky,
而你确实如此
which you are.
杰米叔叔要带你去他的实验室了
Uncle Jimmy is gonna take you to his lab.
等下
Hang on.
见鬼 有条子跟在我们后面
Ah, shit. We got bacon on our tail.
拔出来 把它放好
Unplug yourself. Put that away.
里面有衣服 穿上卫衣
There's some clothes in there. Put the hoodie on.
妈的 来不及了 该死
Shit. There's not enough time. Fuck it.
就用包盖住血吧
Just cover the blood up with your bag.
保持冷静 让我来处理 好吗
Just stay calm and let me handle this, yeah?
直接罚款吧
就是这样…
That's how it goes...
混蛋
Bollocks.
该死的阿肯 贿赂…
Fucking Akan, paying off the...
你知道祖国俄罗斯怎么了吗
太他妈热了
如你所愿
我曾负责这一切 而现在…
我不得不伤害你 亨利
I'm gonna have to hurt you, Henry,
但这是为了你好 伙计
but it's for your own good, mate.
把你的手臂给我 嘿 妈的
Just give me your arm... hey! Shit!
是我 杰米 我们在他们过来之前
It's me! It's Jimmy. We've only got a few moments until
没多少时间了 伙计
they run into they're onto us again, mate.
好了 把你的手臂给我
Just... okay, just give me your arm.
好了 放松
Okay, just relax.
在这 在这
There Here it is. Here it is.
没错
Bingo!
他们就是用这该死的小东西在跟踪你
This little fucker is how they've been tracking you.
再见
Toodle-oo.
片刻之后 你的机械部件
In a few moments, your mechanical parts are gonna
会开始逐渐失灵
start shutting down.
你朋友阿肯有个重要的俄国联络人
Your friend Akan's got an important Russian connection
叫斯列克·迪米奇 斯利克管理阿肯的
named Slick Dimitry. Slick handles all Akan's
警方事宜 枪支事宜 房产事宜等等
cops, guns, real estate, a lot of other shit.
地图上的这个指示点是斯列克的家
This helpful dot on the map is Slick's place.
你要做的就是闯进去 杀了他
All you gotta do is break in there, kill him,
打开他的胸腔 取出他跳动的心脏
open up his ribcage, take out his beating heart,
然后他妈的吃掉
and fucking eat it.
我在开玩笑 我在开玩笑
I'm kidding! I'm kidding.
你不用吃他的心脏
You don't have to fucking eat his heart.
他的心脏之下 是他的供电泵
Under his heart is his charge pump, yeah?
把那东西带给我
Bring that to me.
用上这个 我会打你电话
Use this and I'll contact you on this.
那是我见过的最基的夹克
That has gotta be the gayest jacket I've ever seen.
好棒的夹克 我在哪能买到
我会联系你的
I'll be in touch.
你
过来
你有打火机吗
你他妈觉得我装备武器是干嘛的
现在你可以走了
你想抽吗
想
亨利 阿肯已经开始了
Henry. Akan's already started.
如果我们不阻止他 他很快就会有一支军队
If we don't stop him, he'll have his army in days or sooner.
你是一半机器 一半怂包
You're half machine, half pussy.
等等 等等 我能告诉你些非常重要的事
Wait, wait. I can tell you something very important,
关于派你来的人
about the man who sent you here.
喂 亨利 我在一个高端场所里
Oi, Henry. I'm at this high-class establishment.
朝着那个点走 到了就敲门环
Follow the dot and then just knock on the knocker.
明白吗 敲门环
Get it? Knock on the knocker!
艾拉
艾拉 你个贱人
把他带到杰米那
这是杰米吗
你好 我他妈是一辆车 宝贝
Hi. I'm a fucking car, baby.
雷克萨斯敞篷车
Lexus convertible!
我可不会回里面 那东西是毁灭者级别的
好棒 爽 太棒了
Oh, that's good. Yeah, yeah.
天呐 太棒了 爽
Oh, God, that's amazing. Yeah!
伙计 你来晚了 你来晚了
Fellow, you're late! You're late!
最后十五分钟
The last 15 minutes have been
我的情绪跌宕起伏 伙计
a fucking rollercoaster of emotions for me, mate.
我不清楚还能不能见到你
I didn't know if I was ever gonna see you again.
所以我吸了些这玩意儿
So I fired up some of this shit.
鼻子里好刺激
Fire up my fucking nose, yeah?
不过你来了
But there you are.
没事的 你只是在失去电能 来 嘿
It's okay, Henry. You just lost power. Come on. Hey, there!
女士们 拿些那种烈性的俄国玩意儿来
Bring me some of that strong Russian shit, ladies.
好了 泵在哪
Okay, now where's that booster pump?
在哪 你拿到了吗 你拿到那该死的…
Where is it? Did you get it? Did you get the fucking...
太好了
Yeah! Fucking hell.
就是它 就是它
This is it. This is it, yeah?
好了 等下
Okay, hang on.
好了 拿好 女士 见鬼
Okay, hold this, lady. Shit.
好了 我得把这小玩意儿弄进去
Okay, I gotta get this little fucker in there.
我在开什么玩笑 我这状态办不到
Who am I kidding? I'm in no condition to do this.
抱歉 我这状态没法弄 伙计
I'm sorry. I'm in no condition to do this, mate.
我不在状态
I'm in no condition.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我这状态弄不了
I'm in no condition to do this.
他的手怎么了
他是什么人 他是个机器人吗
他好帅
我知道怎么让他感觉更好
我知道个更好的办法
抬起他
天呐
Oh, goodness.
天呐 你做了什么
Oh, goodness, what have you done?
这次你做了什么 杰米
What have you done this time, Jimmy?
你还有意识吗
Are you still conscious?
很好 嘿 你会好的
Yeah. Hello. You're gonna be okay.
我要给注入你点电能
Just gotta get a little bit of power into you.
女士们 能给我们点空间吗
Ladies, could you give us a bit of space, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
你很了不起 你知道吗
You're a big deal, you know?
你不是唯一被阿肯害的
You're not the only one wronged by Akan.
你和我都有同一个目标
You and I both want the same thing.
这或许会有点疼
This might hurt a bit.
好了
There we go.
太好了
That's wonderful.
现在我能带你回我的实验室了
Now I can take you back to my lab.
对了 我叫杰米
I'm Jimmy, by the way.
我明白 你对这一切很困惑
I realize this is all very confusing for you.
但…
Um, but...
但在我实验室里告诉你会清楚些
but it's better if I show you at the lab, yes...
你好
Hello?
谢谢
Oh, spasiba.
他们在这里了
They're here.
他们肯定跟踪你了 我不能…
They must've followed you. I can't...
我不能让他们看到我这个样子
I can't let them see me like this.
我不能…我很抱歉
I can't let... I'm sorry. I...
我不能待在这 亨利 抱歉
I can't stay here, Henry. I'm sorry.
见鬼
Ah, shit.
太棒了
Fuck yeah!
太棒了 阿肯的手下来了
Fuck yeah, Akan's boys are here.
我要干掉他们 我要干掉他们
I'm gonna hold them off, yeah? I'm gonna hold them off, yeah?
抽屉里有枪拿
More guns for you in the drawer, yeah?
开战了 宝贝
This is fucking war, baby, yeah!
太棒了
Oh, fuck yeah!
好啊 女士们
Hi, ladies.
下层
再见
我他妈搞得定啊
I fucking had that!
我不是他们一伙的
上 上 上
Go, go, go!
这地板就是该死的岩浆 我要烧了它
The floor is fucking lava! I'm gonna burn it!
欧尔佳 卡佳
Oh, Olga, Katya!
杰米 你个混蛋
求你了 请别伤害我
Oh, please, please! Please don't hurt me.
我有家庭
I've got a family.
她是你的妻子吗
Is that your wife?
别担心她 亨利
Don't mind her, Henry.
她在悼念她已故的丈夫
She's mourning her late husband.
没想到还会见到你
I wasn't betting on seeing you again.
你的韧劲真是无与伦比
Your persistence is unparalleled.
也相当令人兴奋
And quite exciting.
斯列克·迪米奇效力得非常出色
Slick Dimitry's services were excellent.
很高兴我没提前付钱
I'm just glad I never paid upfront.
我会告诉艾丝黛尔你做得很好
I'll tell Estelle you did well.
阿肯 阿肯 你他妈开门 听到没
Akan! Akan, open this fucking door, do you hear me?
她打扮得美美的 在楼下我卡车的后车厢里
I got her all dolled up in the back of my truck downstairs.
我要撕裂你的肺
I'm gonna rip your fucking lungs out!
你会走得很远 亨利 而不会像这坨屎
You'll go far, Henry, unlike this piece of shit.
嗨 亨利
Hey, Henry.
把枪放下 没事的
Put your gun down. It's all good.
嘿 嘿 嘿 和睦 和睦
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Peaceful, peaceful.
别激动 冷静
Chill out. Calm down.
我跟你分享了
Now I've shared something with you.
我要你也跟我分享
I need you to share something with me.
阿肯在往哪去
Where's Akan going?
你想找阿肯？
这就是你的阿肯
妈的
Ah, shit.
你的阿肯在这
现在是我的自我在和你的说话
Now that is my ego talking to yours.
你要哪个…
What do you want...
高我  自我？
higher self, ego?
Higher self, ego?
高我
Higher self!
高我 好的
Higher self. Yeah. Okay.
阿肯的护送队在带那女孩去他基地
Akan's convoy are taking the girl to his base.
见鬼 让我来处理 让我来处理
Oh, shit. Let me handle this. Let me handle this.
你他妈干了什么
我们所有的姑娘都死了
好吗？
这他妈可不好
- 那些家伙是什么人  - 好是什么意思
- 你在叫我们放松吗  - 他在叫我们放松
- 亨利？亨利是谁  - 你看到楼上的事没
我很抱歉你们很难过 好吗
I'm sorry you're upset, okay?
你他妈在看什么
亨利和我要去对付阿肯
Henry and I are gonna go deal with Akan.
亨利？谁是亨利
Henry? Who is Henry?
- 你看到楼上的事没  - 你看到你干了什么没
- 你真是个白痴  - 我们和你们一起去干死他们
- 你知道你造成了什么痛苦吗  - 那个白发怂包死定了
他们要为此付出代价
你们要开摩托吗 你们能开摩托去
You wanna go on a the bike? You can go on a the bike.
你们想去？
Just... just... yeah, you wanna go?
好的 开你们的摩托去 该死的
Yeah, yeah, go on your bike. Fucking hell.
有时候同意会让事情变得更容易
Sometimes it's easier just to say yes.
亨利 接好
Henry, catch!
天呐 亨利 我以为我永远失去你了
God, I thought I lost you forever, Henry.
我那时好害怕 你摔下去时 我好害怕
I was so scared. I was so scared when you fell.
我以为永远见不到你了
I thought I would never see you again.
我爱你 亨利
I love you, Henry.
我爱你
I love you.
真是甜蜜
How sweet.
要是我把这一刻放进一杯茶中
If I took this moment and put it in a cup of tea,
我连糖都不用加了
I wouldn't need sugar.
尤里 有劳了
Yuri, pozhaluysta.
现在可以走了
俄国每年有十万根棒球棍售出
Each year, 100,000 baseball bats are sold in Russia
而棒球 最多五十个
and, at most, 50 baseballs.
这让你对伟大俄国的休闲活动有了个主意
Gives you an idea of a great Russian pastime.
这是一根稀有的残存球棍
This is a rare surviving bat.
艾丝黛尔
Estelle.
你能行行好站起来吗
Would you please be so kind and stand up?
还是你想代替她？
Or do you want to take her place?
艾丝黛尔 你男人真是个白衣骑士
Estelle, your boy's quite the white knight,
牺牲自己 让你活下去 只是为了让我的鸡巴
sacrificing himself to keep you alive only for my dick...
以后再杀你
to kill you later.
你确定吗 亨利
Are you sure, Henry?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我没听到说不
聪明
Brilliant!
过来 亨利
Uh, come over here, Henry.
来啊 来啊 来啊 亨利
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, Henry.
你个…
You...
…小…
...little...
…怂包
...pussy.
先生们 请去查看下
不许动
给和平一个机会 兄弟们
Give peace a chance, brothers.
我的自我想杀了你们 但我的高我并不想
My ego wants to kill you But my higher self doesn't.
天呐 宝贝 我在和那家伙说话呢
Jesus, baby. I was talking to that man.
看
Look at this.
这家伙有个记忆阻断器
Dude's got a memory blocker.
我只能为你做这些了 伙计
Well, that's about all I can do for you, mate.
该重启了
Time for a reboot.
十五分钟后见 但愿可以
See you in about 15 minutes, hopefully.
嘿
Hey.
他醒了
He's awake.
你的双眼或许有点很模糊
Your eyes might be a bit blurry.
那只是你的景深感觉在试图校准
It's just your depth perception trying to calibrate, yeah?
跟我走
Follow me as I walk, yeah?
起来
Get up.
好的
Okay.
好了
All right.
你对着我这边 聚得了焦吗
Now, can you focus on me over here?
可以吗
Yeah?
埋葬你 就好比埋葬财宝
Burying you. It's like burying treasure.
真不明白阿肯怎么想的 因为…
I really don't understand what Akan is thinking because...
亨利 别晃悠了 你快到了 伙计
Henry, stop dicking around. You're almost there, mate.
这是你要去的地方 快点
Here's where you gotta get to. Chop Chop.
嘘 是我 杰米  快走
Shh. It's me, Jimmy. Move.
见鬼 那些猪又来了
Oh, shit. Those pigs are here again.
别危及我的实验室
Don't compromise my lab.
让他们离开
Let them leave.
宝贝 呕反射是心理上的 都是你脑子里的
亨利 不要 我命令…妈的
Henry, no. I'm instructing... shit.
离开
干得好 查理·布朗森
Good job, Charlie Bronson.
B2-0！
Bravo 2-0.
开灯
Lights up.
播放视频
Play video.
暮光黎明 一个半机体时代
Dawn of Twilight... a cyborg era.
谢谢你 先生 我对士兵做了脑叶切断术
Thank you, sir. I've lobotomized everything not essential...
切除了所有不必要的东西
not essential to soldiers.
个人记忆 语音 味觉…
Personal memories, speech, sense of taste...
都没了 可能还有点
it's all gone. May still have a bit of
情感激励的问题…
an issue with emotional motivation, which...
激励？试试你的薪水 杰姆斯
Motivation? Try your fucking paycheck, James.
我的薪水…好的
My paych... yes, okay.
这他妈什么情况 杰姆斯
What the shit fuck, James?
抱歉 先生 抱歉 见鬼
I'm sorry, sir! I'm so sorry! Oh, shit!
开门 请开门
Open the doors! Please! Open the door!
机能失常了 让我出去 求你了 我会修正的
We've got a malfunction! Let me out, please! Uh, I'll fix it.
我对此表示怀疑
I doubt it.
该死的白痴
Fucking idiot.
杰米 打断脊柱这种事
You know, Jimmy, something about a spine snapping...
永不过时
it never gets old.
那声音就像…
It sounds like...
结尾 开头 还是它们都一样？
The end, the beginning. Or are they the same?
请坐 亨利
Have a seat, Henry.
一个男人残废后 所有人的脑海里
When a man is first crippled, there's always one question on
总会有一个问题 尤其是他的…
everyone's mind, especially his...
他的鸡巴还能用吗
does his dick work?
我的不能用了 所以我计划逃离这把椅子
Mine didn't, so I plotted my escape from this chair.
西方禁止坏死组织复苏时
I had come to Russia when the west banned resuscitation
我来到了俄国
of cadaver tissue.
阿肯是个疯子 但我的研究有了资助
Akan's a megalomaniac, but my research was funded.
我一直盯着诺贝尔奖
I kept my eyes on the Nobel Prize.
有钱 鸡巴又能用时 谁有空在意恶心的道德伦理
Who has time for icky ethics when he's rich and his cock works, eh?
我付出了高昂的代价
I paid a high price.
我停止了制造士兵 然后我成功了
I stopped making soldiers and then I succeeded.
我培育了用半机体肉身做的人
I grew men made of cyber flesh. Really.
就是高级假体做的 但千万别告诉…
Just fancy pants prostheses, but don't dare tell my...
我的替身们
My avatars!
另一方面 半机器人都有数位和一个大脑
Now, cyborgs, on the other hand, have bits and a brain.
他们独立思考 至少理论上是这样
They think for themselves, in theory at least.
我能看看你吗
Shall we have a look at you?
那个嬉皮士 总抽大麻
That hippie, always with the ganja.
(已连接新设备)
你没抽吧
You're not baked, are you?
但愿没
Hope not.
好了
Right.
你太棒了 亨利
You are the man, Henry.
当然 没剩多少真实人体了
Mm, there's very little actual man left, of course.
骨骼肌肉系统都增强了 心血管涡轮
Enhanced skeletal muscular systems, cardiovascular turbo
由锔二四四原子电池驱动
boosted with a curium 244 atomic battery.
晚上好好睡一觉  你能驱动一艘航空母舰
A good night of sleep and you'd power an aircraft carrier.
非凡的技术 对吗
Remarkable technology, is it not?
(初始化)
不是你
... Not you.
是我的孩子们
My boys.
我制造了最初几个来复仇 但后来我开始了
I made the first few for revenge but then I started
自我新层面的探索 我能抿一口吗
exploring new aspects of myself. Can I have a sip?
过去几年 我过上了真正的生活 亨利
I have lived these past years, Henry.
我的小伙子们 他们收到了超速罚单
My lads, they get speeding tickets, they walk barefoot
赤脚走在草地上 还滚了床单
through the grass, and boy, do they get laid.
你绝猜不到 我们独自在这时会做什么
You'll never guess what we do here sometimes alone.
按播放 在那边 去吧
Hit play. Over there. Go on.
我爱你入骨
I got you under my skin
你就在我心深处
I got you deep in the heart of me
你如此深入我心
So deep in my heart
成了我真实的一部分
that you're really a part of me
我爱你入骨
I got you under my skin
我不想放弃
I tried so not to give in
我告诉自己此等情事
I say to myself this affair
永不会一帆风顺
never will go so well
可我为何要抗拒
Why should I try to resist
我明明知道
when baby I know so well
我爱你入骨
I got you under my skin
传输进行中
你干了什么 伙计
What have you done,mate?
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
闭上眼睛 你有些问题 伙计
Close your eyes. Something's wrong with you, mate.
别担心 不是癌症 淋病什么的
Don't worry, it's not cancer the clap or nothing.
只是要你坐到这椅子上
Just gonnagotta sit you down in this chair and take a look
检查下你 扫描器说 你极为危险
at you, yeah? The scan says you're in terrible danger.
你个该遭千刀万剐的叛徒 你个骗人的畜生
Of being shivved for being a traitor, you lying grasser!
我要把你关闭 伙计
I'm shutting you down, mate.
把原型体宝宝放下
Put down the proto baby.
快
Now!
我们即使知道你向阿肯
We tried to unplug you nicely even though we knew that you
进行了视讯传输 也还想友好地关掉你
beamed your video to Akan.
没有？
No?
这是什么
What's this?
那是什么
What's that?
你向阿肯传输了
You're broadcasting it that to Akan!
够了
Enough!
Enough.
即使我相信你 我还是要…
Even if I did believe you, you still have to...
该死 亨利 别
Fuck! No, Henry, no!
不要
No!!!!!
你把他们带到我实验室了 我竟然信任你
You brought them to my lab! I trusted you!
亨利 请你杀了我 阿肯不会杀我
Henry, please kill me? Akan won't.
他会让我活在这身腐烂的
He'll make me live in this straightjacket of rotten,
有着恶臭皮肤的束衣中 我之前到底在想什么
smelly skin! What the fuck was I thinking that
阿肯的玩具机器人是我朋友？
Akan's toy robot was my friend?
谢谢你 亨利
Thank you, Henry.
也去你妈的 但谢意占多数
Fuck you, too, but mostly thanks.
我的实验室处于危险之中 但我能用阿肯的
My lab's compromised, but I can build a new one using Akan's
设备造一个新的 我们一起去救你妻子就行了 对吗
equipment when we go get your wife together, right?
嘿 把那放置在墙上
Hey, put that on the wall.
我要是无法拥有我的实验室 那没人能拥有她
If I can't have my lab, no one's having her.
别丢了这东西
Now, don't lose this.
去你妈的 阿肯
Fuck you, Akan.
别改频道
And don't change your channel.
我们来了
We're coming right over.
好了 我数到有六辆车
Right, I counted six vehicles.
至少有三十五个人
That's at least 35 men.
在他们进入旅馆前 我们得把他们的人数减半
We've gotta cut them down to half that before they enter the
那样我们才有机会一战 活着出去
hotel to give us a fighting chance to get out alive.
还有 喜欢音乐剧的家伙都会
Also, there's a certain stigma attached to blokes who
被扣上某个污名 现在我只想说清楚
like musicals. I just wanna get it out there right
我直得跟箭一样 明白吗
now that I'm straight as an arrow. Got it?
他们来了
Here they come.
等等
Wait for it.
就现在
Now.
好了 掩护我
Right, cover me.
该死 他们在旅馆里了
Fuck, they're in the hotel.
我们也不再需要狙击手了
We don't need the sniper anymore either.
进去 会见上校
Go inside. See the colonel.
这里 小伙子 全副武装起来
Over here, laddie. Arm yourself to the teeth.
别碰这个 埃玛济是我的
Don't touch that. Emma Gee is mine.
我父亲曾说
That's what my father used to say...
一天一颗手榴弹 牵制住敌人
'A grenade a day keeps the enemy at bay.'
来吧 快
Come along. Chop, chop.
大萨利
Big Sally.
家是战争所在的地方
Uh, well, home is where the battle is.
好了 列兵 我们的职责是保证残疾人士不受伤害
Right, private, it is our duty to ensure that no harm comes
明白吗
to the cripple, understood?
跟好了
Follow on.
你能听见他们 但你打不到
If you can hear them, but you can't shoot them,
或许你能炸他们 剥个鸡蛋扔下去 小伙子
you can probably grenade them. Drop an egg down there, laddie.
前进
Forward.
来
Come along.
天呐 真是尴尬
Good lord, how embarrassing.
刚躲过了一发子弹
Dodged a bullet on that one.
我掩护你
I'll cover you.
你跑向他们
You go around them.
别让残疾人士倒在你的脚下 小伙子
Don't let the cripple get below you, laddie!
很好
Jolly good.
等下  来帮下残疾人士
Hold on, wait. Help me with the cripple.
我一示意 你就退后五步 小伙子
Retreat five paces back on my command, laddie.
一个残疾人住在一个破地方
谢谢你 尤里 我的总部其实在上面
Spasibo, Yuri. My quarters are actually up there.
你们想看看吗
Would you like to see them?
我们会看的
Oh, we will.
确实会
Indeed.
开足马力
Don't spare the horses.
走下一个滑道
Take the next slipway.
就那边
Off, here. Here we go.
稳住 小伙子
Hang on, laddie.
我们来扭转局面 干翻那些混蛋
Let's turn the tables on these buggers.
呔嗬
Tally ho.
大本钟
Big Ben.
阿肯是个贱货
Akan is a cunt!!
天呐
Oh, my.
看来阿肯已经开始了
Looks like Akan's already begun.
最迟明天  那些可怜家伙就会变成
By tomorrow, these poor chaps will be super
你这样的超级机器人士兵 当心
robotic soldiers like yourself. Look out!
什么是红色的而且对你的牙齿不好
站起来 小伙子
On your feet, lad.
你左边
On your left.
等下
Hang on.
我帮你争取些时间
I'm gonna buy you some time!
封上门
Seal the door.
你不知道我有多少次都梦见
Can't tell you the number of times I've dreamt that I was
自己乘着这电梯上楼
riding up in this lift.
真遗憾 我不能…
It's a pity I can't...
起落装置而已 小伙子
It's just the landing gear, laddie.
现在 听我说
Now, listen to me.
等你杀了阿肯  我要你直视他的眼睛
When you kill Akan, I want you to look him right in those eyes
直到他身体其他地方 都死透了 明白吗
until the rest of him is just as dead as they are, understood?
不行  我恐怕不能跟你一起去了
No, I'm afraid I shall not be coming with.
但你让我带你走了这么远 这给了一个老兵
But you letting me get you this far has given an old sweat his
他一生中最盛大的礼物
grandest gift in all his years.
别
No.
卡在他的颈静脉里了
It's lodged in his jugular.
如果你拔出 我就没法…
If you uncork it, I won't be able to...
那个…
The...
你口袋里的那个啥 快
the thingamajig in your pocket, quickly.
我恐怕要坦白些事
Afraid I have a confession to make.
瞧 我监视阿肯好多年了
See, I've been surveilling Akan for years.
所以当你摔落到那条车道上 如此精彩地
So when you dropped down onto that roadway and went rogue so
出手相向时 我所看到的是我美好的复仇机会
magnificently, well, all I saw was a nice my shot at revenge.
迪米奇的事 你证明了我是对的 然后在森林…
You proved me right with Dimitry, but then in the forest,
我注意到了一个植入物
well, I noticed an implant.
一个记忆阻断器 明白吗
A memory block, see?
我承受不起让你想起在别处
And I couldn't afford to have you remember a better life
有过美好生活的代价 所以我就留它在里面了
somewhere else. So I left it in.
我恐怕那样很不光彩
Not my finest hour, I'm afraid.
但之后在我的实验室里 我试图分析
But then back at my lab when I was trying to analyze
你能为我做什么的时候
what you could do for me,
我意识到了 你对我来说…
I realized who you are...
是什么人 亨利
to me. Henry.
有个朋友真的很棒 亨利
It's bloody nice having a friend, Henry.
你会认为那些死 会让我对此做好了准备
You'd think all those deaths would've prepared me for this.
如果你还没有
If you haven't already,
你现在就要开始想起你过去的时刻 亨利
you'll start to remember bits from your past now, Henry.
那些记忆 它们是真实的
And those memories, they're real.
它们是你
They're you.
相信它们
Trust them.
记忆 记忆 记忆
Memories, memories, memories.
我的第一批半机体士兵
My first batch of cyber soldiers.
他们大脑的残存部分 被上传了你今天
With everything that you have experienced today uploaded into
所经历的一切 他们只记得在实验室里醒来
what's left of their brains, all they remember is waking up in
他们的妻子在给他们旋上腿
the lab with their wife screwing their legs on.
我爱你 查理
I love you, Charlie.
我爱你 爱德华
I love you, Edward.
我爱你 托马斯
I love you, Thomas.
你认得这个吗
You recognize these?
不认得？
No?
奇怪
That's odd.
是你妻子的
They're your wife's.
我闻得出你喜欢她些什么
Mm, I smell what you like about her.
这一个就快为你做好准备了
This one is almost ready for you.
但我提醒你
But I'm warning you,
他们的推动器让你的那个…
their boosters make the one you have now...
看上去像块该死的九伏电池
You look like a fucking 9 volt.
上 狠狠干他
Go ahead and fuck him up.
起来
Get up.
Get up!
肾上腺素
你能应对这个吗
Can you handle this?
亨利
Henry.
你干嘛打你自己呢 亨利
Why are you hitting yourself, Henry?
嗯？
Hmm?
宝贝 宝贝 你没事吧
Baby? Baby, are you okay?
我喜欢你对我那么呵护
I love how protective you are of me.
你欠我一个道歉
You owe me an apology.
什么道歉
For?
怀疑我的道歉
Doubting me.
我是有一定忧虑
I did have certain apprehensions.
那你为什么让我那么做
Why'd you let me do it?
只是为了满足我女人 我失去了所有手下
I was just entertaining my woman and losing all of my men.
所有人都死了吗
Is everybody dead?
- 是的  - 是的
- Yes.  - Yes.
你知道我什么时候意识到这能成的吗
Do you know when I realized this was working?
什么时候
When?
亨利把我拉进他逃生舱 不惜一切
When Henry pulled me into the escape pod, trying to get me out
想把我弄出实验室的时候
of the lab no matter what.
谁会想到那怂包会是个该死的激励者
Who would've thought that pussy is a hell of a motivator?
我们明天会有数百个你 下周数千个
We'll have a hundred of you tomorrow, a thousand next week.
每一个的第一个记忆都会是他的妻子
Each one's first memory will be his wife
把一枚廉价的铜戒戴在他的手指上
slipping a cheap brass ring on his finger.
我的每一个士兵 醒来都会愿意
Every single one of my soldiers will awake willing to do
做我聪明的妻子要求做的任何事 无论是进军到
anything my brilliant wife tells him, whether it's marching on
巴黎还是白宫草坪
Paris or the White House lawn.
我会假装你理解你所扮演的角色
I would like to pretend you understand the part you played.
你没有创造历史 亨利
You didn't make history, Henry.
而是帮忙结束了
You helped end it.
你个…
You...
…小…
...little...
…怂包
...pussy.
我老头就那么称呼我
That's what my old man called me.
就好像那是我的名字
It's like it was my name.
我杀了所有错的人 证明他是对的
And I proved him right by killing all the wrong people.
我爱你 亨利 除了你名字外 我从没叫过你别的
I love you, Henry, and I'll never call you anything but your
但你必须决定
name, but you gotta decide...
你要躺在那儿 把血咽进嘴里
are you gonna lay there, swallow that blood in your mouth?
还是站起来吐掉血 去让他们流血
Or are you gonna stand up, spit it out, and go spill theirs?
阿肯
Akan!
你个该死的…
You fuck...
别这样
No!
住手
Stop!
我命令你住手
I am ordering you to stop!
亨利
Henry!
住手
Stop!!!
他在哪
Where is he?
不
No.
去你妈的 混蛋
Fuck you, motherfucker!
去你妈的
Fuck you!
亨利 你怎么能对我这样
How could you do this to me, Henry?
你他妈怎么能这样
How could you fucking do this?
回答我
Answer me!
冷静
混蛋
Motherfucker!
怎么回事 亨利
What happened, Henry?
你应当爱我
You were supposed to love me.
亨利
Henry!
听从你的心声
Listen to your heart!
译者/微博@Emtee
字幕转制：天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者